[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Osteology is an important part of physical and forensic anthropology. What does an osteologist study?", "correct_answer": "bones", "incorrect_answers": ["skulls", "blood", "dead  bodies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of alcoholic beverage is the traditional Thai drink Sang Som?", "correct_answer": "Rum", "incorrect_answers": ["Beer", "Wine", "Brandy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2006 a female corpse dating from the 16th century was found near Venice. According to archaeologists the presence of this object in the corpses mouth was the result of a vampire-slaying ritual.", "correct_answer": "A brick", "incorrect_answers": ["An animal bones", "A glass piece", "A crucifix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is a world landmark that was NOT destroyed by George in his Rambo daydream sequence from the Weird Al Yankovic movie UHF?", "correct_answer": "Leaning Tower of Pisa", "incorrect_answers": ["Hollywood Sign", "Colosseum", "Eiffel tower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is mainly used in literature to refer to a group of crows?", "correct_answer": "A murder", "incorrect_answers": ["A mug", "A plunder", "A gaggle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress played the character of Pussy Galore in the motion picture Goldfinger?", "correct_answer": "Honor Blackman", "incorrect_answers": ["Diane Baker", "Majel Barrett", "Eunice Gayson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed the unforgettable Cruella de Vil in the 1996 Walt Disney movie 101 Dalmatians?", "correct_answer": "Glenn Close", "incorrect_answers": ["Kathleen Turner", "Meryl Streep", "Anjelica Huston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unit in the metric system do astronomers use to measure the wavelength of light?", "correct_answer": "nanometer", "incorrect_answers": ["eccentricity", "photon", "equant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the Nintendo system debut in the U.S.A.?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1998", "1980", "1970"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actor voiced Sheriff Woody in the 1995 animated movie Toy Story?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Penn", "Robin Williams", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To prevent rice from sticking, you should do this.", "correct_answer": "Stir", "incorrect_answers": ["Saute on low heat", "Add some salt", "Pour additional water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The moves in this sport include Barani, Triffus, Miller, and Randy.", "correct_answer": "Trampoline", "incorrect_answers": ["Figure Skating", "Ballroom Dancing", "BMX"]}]